<application>
  <component name="AppStorage">
    <histories>
      <item value="ompletions Amount" />
      <item value="completions Amount" />
      <item value="Completions Amount" />
      <item value="Amount" />
      <item value="set Completions Amount" />
      <item value="completions" />
      <item value="line Height" />
      <item value="bar" />
      <item value="bar Height" />
      <item value="all Width" />
      <item value="full Width" />
      <item value="full Length" />
      <item value="Draw the specified circle using the specified paint. If radius is &lt;= 0, then nothing will be drawn. The circle will be filled or framed based on the Style in the paint." />
      <item value="serial Number" />
      <item value="Assigns the specified Object reference to each element of the specified range of the specified array of Objects. The range to be filled extends from index fromIndex, inclusive, to index toIndex, exclusive. (If fromIndex==toIndex, the range to be filled is empty.)" />
      <item value="node Texts" />
      <item value="node Amount" />
      <item value="node Num" />
      <item value="结点" />
      <item value="Converts an unpacked complex data value holding a dimension to its final floating point value. The two parameters unit and value are as in TYPE_DIMENSION." />
      <item value="Progress Bar" />
      <item value="Form Body" />
      <item value="require Non Null" />
      <item value="login Core" />
      <item value="core Login" />
      <item value="main Login" />
      <item value="reconnecting" />
      <item value="available Heartbeat" />
      <item value="available" />
      <item value="fail" />
      <item value="filed" />
      <item value="heartbeat Connection" />
      <item value="Returns nanoseconds since boot, including time spent in sleep." />
      <item value="elapsed nanoseconds since boot." />
      <item value="If set, and the activity being launched is already running in the current task, then instead of launching a new instance of that activity, all of the other activities on top of it will be closed and this Intent will be delivered to the (now on top) old activity as a new Intent. For example, consider a task consisting of the activities: A, B, C, D. If D calls startActivity() with an Intent that resolves to the component of activity B, then C and D will be finished and B receive the given Intent, resulting in the stack now being: A, B. The currently running instance of activity B in the above example will either receive the new intent you are starting here in its onNewIntent() method, or be itself finished and restarted with the new intent. If it has declared its launch mode to be &quot;multiple&quot; (the default) and you have not set FLAG_ACTIVITY_SINGLE_TOP in the same intent, then it will be finished and re-created; for all other launch modes or if FLAG_ACTIVITY_SINGLE_TOP is set then this Intent will be delivered to the current instance's onNewIntent(). This launch mode can also be used to good effect in conjunction with FLAG_ACTIVITY_NEW_TASK: if used to start the root activity of a task, it will bring any currently running instance of that task to the foreground, and then clear it to its root state. This is especially useful, for example, when launching an activity from the notification manager." />
      <item value="ignore Case" />
      <item value="Case" />
      <item value="verification Input" />
      <item value="correct Input" />
      <item value="Creates a new random number generator using a single long seed. The seed is the initial value of the internal state of the pseudorandom number generator which is maintained by method next. The invocation new Random(seed) is equivalent to:" />
      <item value="Creates a new random number generator. This constructor sets the seed of the random number generator to a value very likely to be distinct from any other invocation of this constructor" />
      <item value="remove Chars" />
      <item value="remove Small Letter" />
      <item value="remove Capital Letter" />
      <item value="Image Captcha" />
      <item value="This can only be used in conjunction with FLAG_ACTIVITY_NEW_TASK." />
      <item value="If set, this activity will become the start of a new task on this history stack. A task (from the activity that started it to the next task activity) defines an atomic group of activities that the user can move to. Tasks can be moved to the foreground and background; all of the activities inside of a particular task always remain in the same order. See Tasks and Back Stack for more information about tasks. This flag is generally used by activities that want to present a &quot;launcher&quot; style behavior: they give the user a list of separate things that can be done, which otherwise run completely independently of the activity launching them. When using this flag, if a task is already running for the activity you are now starting, then a new activity will not be started; instead, the current task will simply be brought to the front of the screen with the state it was last in. See FLAG_ACTIVITY_MULTIPLE_TASK for a flag to disable this behavior. This flag can not be used when the caller is requesting a result from the activity being launched." />
      <item value="FLAG ACTIVITY NEW TASK" />
      <item value="MULTIPLE" />
      <item value="MULTIPLE_" />
    </histories>
    <option name="languageScores">
      <map>
        <entry key="CHINESE" value="433" />
        <entry key="ENGLISH" value="434" />
        <entry key="DANISH" value="1" />
        <entry key="GERMAN" value="4" />
        <entry key="MALAYALAM" value="1" />
        <entry key="BENGALI" value="1" />
        <entry key="PORTUGUESE" value="1" />
        <entry key="INDONESIAN" value="2" />
      </map>
    </option>
  </component>
  <component name="Settings">
    <option name="baiduTranslateSettings">
      <app-key>
        <option name="appId" value="20200918000568375" />
      </app-key>
    </option>
    <option name="ignoreRegExp" value="" />
    <option name="youdaoTranslateSettings">
      <youdao-translate>
        <option name="appId" value="2f2d5e6a9f7e1244" />
      </youdao-translate>
    </option>
  </component>
</application>